♪ MTV ♪
[Harry] I'm sorry
about this. Arch.
I always liked you.
Fentanyl. Yes or no?
One hundred percent.
You have to follow the money.
- [door bangs open]
- Armed police! Armed police!
Thank you. Shall we do this?
I'll give you a call.
- Where's my Tommy?
- I don't know.
I'm not fucking clairvoyant.
Why don't you get your son
to come and say that to my face?
Move Eddie to the Cotswolds.
The Harrigan Express is
running out of steam.
When it does. a lot of people
are gonna go down with it.
I can provide you
with a parachute.
I need to get out of here.
Archie was in with the
Stevensons on the fentanyl.
He was on a percentage.
to keep convincing me
- to leave them to it.
- I'm not sure that that's right.
- You calling Maeve a liar?
- What I'm saying is.
it actually could
be a lot worse.
Unless you bring back
my boy here tonight.
I'm gonna descend
on the Cotswolds
like a plague of
fucking locusts.
- [gun cocks]
- Where's Tommy?
♪ Suspenseful music
[radio host] Good
morning. London.
Look. I know it's gray outside.
and it's super early. it's
just coming up to 6:00.
but if you're with
me. grab a coffee.
maybe grab a pastry.
if you have one.
You are with me. Claude.
and the entire gang.
We'll look after
you. Let's get in...
[car alarms blaring]
- [phone ringing]
- ♪ suspenseful music
[phone ringing. vibrating]
Kev?
[Kevin] Richie's
coming for all of us.
♪
Babe. hey.
- What's wrong?
- You need to get up.
Where's Gina?
You need to get dressed
as quick as you can.
Gina!
[distant] Gina? Gina.
[Gina] What? What's going on?
Harry. you scared
the shit out of me.
She's fine. Hey. babe.
Can you just get dressed?
[Gina] Dad. what is it?
Nothing. We're gonna go
somewhere. that's all.
- Is it the police?
- No. babe. We'll talk.
Just get dressed. put
a little bag together
for overnight. yeah?
[line ringing]
Mike.
Yeah. I know it's
early. I need a favor.
It's a mess. Kerry next door
WhatsApped me some photos.
- She's got a video.
- But Richie didn't know that.
I want everyone on
standby. Call Seraphina...
Because it was on fire. babe.
Tell them to pack a bag
and get here right now.
Yeah. I'll forward them to you.
Richie Stevenson just
blew up Kevin's house.
[Kevin] There's nothing worth
retrieving. It's all gone.
Kev. What's happened?
Hang on.
It's all right. Mum.
Everyone's fine.
Where's Bella?
Hotel. Harry's idea.
Paul. where's Harry?
[Kevin] Bet that's him now.
Look. I'll call you
back. Call you back.
[phone vibrating]
[sighs] Harry.
Kev. Meet me down the
yard. bring Eddie.
No. Dad wants everyone here.
The yard. Kev. Quick as you can.
What's happened?
- [Conrad] What's he saying?
- [Maeve] What...
put him on the speaker.
[Kevin] I'll be there.
Harry wants to meet at the
yard. he says to bring Eddie.
What? I told you. I
want everyone here.
- Dad...
- They just blew
the fucking roof off your gaff.
I want you. Seraphina.
Brendan. everyone. here.
Circle the wagons. now.
Harry's found Tommy.
♪ Fast. pulsing music
- [Harry] You ready?
- Ready for what. Harry?
Tell me what's going on.
I'll tell you if I'm ready.
Harry.
Harry?
Come on. Let's go.
♪
Wake Eddie up.
[Maeve] May I say something?
It's not "Seraphina
and Brendan."
It's "Brendan and Seraphina."
Brendan's our son.
Seraphina's a
ten-second knee-trembler
with a lap dancer in the
bogs at Stringfellows.
So. "Brendan and Seraphina."
not "Seraphina and Brendan."
Well. Seraphina didn't
hand a Swiss banker
a million in cash who vanished.
Seraphina isn't a
useless gobshite
who lost his dad five million
to some Belarusians he met
in the Pimm's marquee
at Wimbledon. Huh?
[vehicle chirps]
[chirps]
Harry?
Drive the car.
Morning. lads. What we doing?
I see. Is that for me?
Are we shooting
families now as well?
I couldn't give a fuck
about your family.
Richie's kid's missing.
so it's an eye
for a fucking eye.
Right.
Well. I can't let
you harm my family.
Hey! Stop fucking about. mate.
[distant shouting]
[engine starts]
You ain't even fucking carrying.
No. you're right.
I'm not. but...
...I do have this.
Can you hear me. Conrad?
[Conrad] Loud
and clear. Harry.
Loud and clear.
Yeah. think about it.
So. you can pull that trigger.
We can do this. right?
But I guarantee you. by
the time you get home.
your girlfriend Sonya.
you'll be pulling her
out the Thames tonight.
And your long-term live-in
common-law partner...
What's her name? Precious?
You'll be lucky if you
find a single hair.
Bit of gristle. tooth.
Yeah?
By tomorrow. your mums. dads.
dogs. cats.
fucking goldfish.
whatever you keep...
This is exactly
what I fucking said.
Shut the fuck up.
I mean. alternatively. you
can just call Richie. right?
And you tell him
you come round here.
you didn't see no one.
If you want. torch
the fucking gaff.
♪
In your own time. boys.
In your own time.
[Harry] What's it gonna be?
Yeah. Yeah. Sorry.
All right. Put it on ice. yeah?
[sniffles]
[door closes]
What the fuck was that?
Halloween. babe. They
got the wrong day.
♪ "Starburster" by
Fontaines D.C. ♪
♪ It may feel bad ♪
♪ I wanna see you alone.
I wanna sharp the stone ♪
♪ I wanna bounce the bone.
I wanna mess with it ♪
♪ I wanna lay the Deville.
the whole crew on the sill ♪
♪ I want the preacher and
pill. I wanna bless with it ♪
♪ I wanna head to a mass
and get cast in it ♪
♪ That shit's funnier
than any A-class. innit? ♪
♪ I wanna talk with the clown
who has apologies down ♪
♪ Pay him 300 pounds
to take a class in it ♪
♪ I wanna bite the phone.
I wanna bleed the tone ♪
♪ I wanna see you alone.
alone. alone. lone ♪
♪ I wanna strait the shark and
find me somewhere to park ♪
♪ Like the light when it's dark.
it's dark. it's dark. dark ♪
♪ A few stars about make
it feel like peace ♪
♪ In a way ♪
♪ A complimentary round ♪
♪ Constellation
got a twist in it ♪
♪ For a GPO and all
the hits in it ♪
♪ I'm gonna hit your business
if it's momentary blissness ♪
Come here. you
bollocks. Come here.
You keep your head
down now. you hear me?
Keep your head
down. Okay? Mm-hmm?
- [Eddie] Hurrah.
- All right.
All right now. Richie will try
and hit the yard next. okay?
- I'll be careful.
- All right.
Okay. keep in touch.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
- Dad.
Okay.
[vehicle door closes]
[engine starts]
[Harry] You all right. Mike?
This is my wife Jan.
Hi. Jan. Nice to meet you.
Gina. this is Mike. He.
uh. he's an old mate.
We're gonna stay on
his boat for a bit.
- Who is Mike?
- I told you.
- he's an old mate.
- Who I've never heard of.
Are you sure you're gonna be
all right with this. Mike?
- Well. to be honest. Harry...
- Yeah? Go on.
- No. [stammers]
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
- Where's Wendy?
- Spain.
- Oh. lovely.
- Yeah.
And the cats just
had a new litter.
- Has she?
- Yeah. Nine kittens.
[gasps] Gina. kittens.
- [Mike] I've left instructions.
- Thanks. Mike.
- Yeah.
- You're a legend.
- Scusa.
- Thank you.
- Who's Mike?
- I said. he's. uh.
- he's an old mate.
- Who's Mike. Harry?
Mike is a renowned journalist...
a sports journalist.
actually... and an author.
He's also a degenerate
gambler. he owes me 30 grand.
Are you gonna tell me
what all this is about?
Yeah. there's a little
bit of a situation. okay?
And as soon as I sort it
out. then... there won't be.
Until then. I think it's best
that you and Gina stay here.
just for a little bit. okay?
It is lovely. Have a
little look around.
- Maria called.
- Yeah?
She went to see her mum.
found her lying in
her own piss and shit.
Oh. no. All right. look.
I said I'll sort
it out. so I will.
I will sort it out. okay?
- Dad?
- Yes.
- Be careful.
- I'll be all right.
Go and see the kittens. That
sounds lovely. doesn't it?
Kittens. eh? See you later.
[Jan] Don't forget that
meeting this morning.
I'll be there.
- Make sure you are. Harry.
- I'll be there.
- This is where you grew up?
- [sighs]
I left as soon as I could.
I was 15.
Couldn't take it anymore.
You couldn't take being rich
and having a beautiful home?
I couldn't take my father.
Can he get us in to
see the prime minister?
You don't need Malcolm to
get you in to see the PM.
I can do that for you.
♪ Suspenseful music
I can get you in to
see anyone you want.
For the proper consideration.
My clients take the view
that if it's worth having.
it's worth paying for.
We are not
communists. after all.
[chuckles]
♪
Did you get it?
- All of it.
- Can I have it?
You will get it as soon
- as I've made a copy.
- What?
Come on.
Mm-mm.
Call it insurance.
I will be in touch.
♪
[Mukasa] We have
eyes on the Audi.
- He's made us.
- [Fisk] Good.
I want him to know we're on him.
[tires screech]
- [Kevin] Where's Jan and Gina?
- Safe and sound. mate.
- Cool.
- How's your house?
It's fucked.
I've been followed.
- Who?
- Fisk.
He's outside the wire. mate.
Morning. Eddie.
Come over here. mate.
- Go on.
- Hop up in here. mate. Go on.
♪ Suspenseful music
♪
Why don't you go down
and take his hood off?
Look. whatever this is. I
had nothing to do with it.
[whimpering]
I've never seen him in my life.
No one said you did.
What's that smell?
Brace yourself. mate.
[Kevin] Fuck me.
Jesus fucking Christ.
♪ Slow. somber music
Do you want to tell
them what you told me?
This one said he'd-he'd pay me
if I took care of
someone for him.
Bollocks.
Said he'd bring this
kid to the club.
Fuck this.
You fucking stay!
Go on.
He stabbed Hughie Campbell
and they ran out the club.
He then texts me and
I pick them both up.
I bring them back to the club.
I leave.
When I return. the kid's dead.
Been stabbed 50. 60 times.
This one's nowhere to be seen.
He's a fucking liar.
How much did he pay you?
Ten grand.
[scoffs]
Fucking cunt!
[Eddie] What the
fuck are you doing?
[grunts] Fuck!
Lift your ass.
[Kevin] Do you know what
you've fucking done?
What the fuck are you doing?
[Kevin] Silly little cunt.
- [Eddie] Fuck off!
- [Kevin] Fucking come with me.
♪ Slow. dark music
- Get off me!
- Cunt!
[drawer closes]
What you gonna do with that?
- This!
- [yelps]
[groans] What the fuck?
[panting]
What the fuck have you done?
- Dad...
- Shut it.
Congratulations. you
dumb little cunt.
Our house. the house
that I paid for.
that you grew up in... my
house... has been bombed.
Harry. Jan and Gina
nearly got fucking killed.
- Are you listening?
- Yes!
Now we'll have to
call in every soldier.
everyone the family's
ever done a favor for.
get them tooled up and get
them out on the streets.
Congratulations.
you've started a war.
Not necessarily.
Not necessarily?
We've just bombed Pearl Harbor.
Mm.
Have you told Dad?
No. He's your boy. I
wanted you to know first.
[sighs]
You fucking little cunt.
[keypad beeping]
[Kevin] Dad? Can you
speak on this phone?
[Conrad over
phone] Hang about.
- Oh. fuck it.
- Who is it?
- Oh. Jesus.
- Who is it. Conrad?
[sighs]
Just give me a chance there.
I fucking know. Maeve. will you?
Okay.
- What's he saying?
- Kevin?
Maeve.
What? Put it on the speaker.
It's a fucking burner.
Give it here.
Kevin? What's happening?
We found Tommy.
Chopped up in a box.
You still there?
- I'm here.
- [Kevin sighs]
He never left the
club that night.
Long story short. whatever
it is you're thinking.
that's what happened.
[sighs] Is he there?
- Yes.
- Put him on.
[phone beeps]
- You're on speaker.
- Uh-huh.
- Who else is there?
- Harry.
Hello. Harry.
- Hello. Conrad.
- Who else?
[Kevin] No. it's just us.
[Conrad exhales]
Eddie?
- Yes. Grandad?
- Eddie.
I want you to listen to me
very. very carefully now.
- Are you listening to me?
- Tell him you're proud.
I am not fucking proud.
Tell him he's a true Harrigan.
Go on. go on. You
know you want to.
[distant horn blows]
[Conrad] Eddie.
We will talk about this later.
[line clicks]
Dad?
Powwow. sauna. five minutes.
Wipe that fucking
smile off your face.
And don't you move
from that seat.
[door closes]
What was that about?
Letting Eddie off
the hook like that.
What's Dad fucking thinking?
We do have an option.
Yeah?
It might work.
It will definitely
buy us some time.
How?
There's no way around this one.
Not unless we stick
that poor cunt in there
back together. there ain't.
But there is an
option. all right?
I-It... [sighs]
It's a bit of a Hail Mary.
It's a bit fucking spicy.
- Go on.
- We've got Valjon. ain't we?
[electricity crackles]
[steam hissing]
The way I see...
[Maeve] Hmm?
...the cleanest and
quickest way to wrap this up
is to take out Richie
and his inner circle.
Yes. but the problem
is. on a slow day.
they're armed to the teeth.
Well. so. we get Kev to
talk to his Czech friends.
We need a list. A hit list.
Who's on the menu?
Well. I say we skip
the appetizers.
and go straight to mains.
- Richie.
- Vron.
What?
As in Tommy's grieving mother?
Mm-hmm.
What? I like Vron.
Yes. I like Vron. She's funny.
Funny? Oh. she's
fucking hilarious.
Yeah. she is. You know
I've always liked her.
But I know how we
can get to her.
How and where.
Besides.
don't you want Richie
to suffer and then die?
Well. if we do Vron.
that'll put you
in the crosshairs.
That'll put you on the board.
Oh. I've always
been on the board.
I am the White Queen. baby.
- [chuckles]
- Let's see if Harry
can get us out of this first.
But we're agreed.
Vron is plan B.
♪ Suspenseful music
[indistinct chatter]
Kiko. stop fucking around. mate.
I need you to get over
to this address. right?
I want footage of the
wife and kids. yeah? Now.
- Now.
- Okay.
Zosia.
Can you take Eddie back
up the Cotswolds. yeah?
He's doing Kevin's tits in.
- On it.
- Thank you.
[phone vibrating]
Oh. Maria.
[Maria] I'm sorry. Mr. Harry.
I know you're always
very busy. it's just...
- I'm here at the care home.
- I am so sorry.
I. um... I missed. um...
- Harry?
- Hang a second.
The Czechs are due any minute.
We've still got the
filth on the doorstep.
Right. okay. Um. is there.
is there any chance
that you can perhaps
put the director on the phone.
I could speak to them now?
They wouldn't see me.
- Who you talking to?
- Maria.
- Who?
- My cleaner.
Okay. um. no. no. uh...
Don't worry.
Right. um... [clears throat]
I'll tell you what. I can
come... I'll come right now.
Uh. I'll be there
in about 20 minutes.
You just. just wait
where you are. yeah?
Okay.
Okay? Okay. bye.
Where you going?
- Old people's home. mate.
- What?
I'll call you when I'm done.
♪ Exciting music
♪
Hi. Maria. Sorry I'm late.
No. Thanks for
coming. Mr. Harry.
Not at all. Um. where are we?
- This way.
- [indistinct chatter]
Hello. I'm Harry Da Souza.
I had a ten o'clock
appointment with you?
I'm sorry. I got
stuck in traffic.
but I was wondering. is
there any chance we could.
- we could still do this?
- [Christine] I'm really sorry.
I can't help you.
As I explained to Mrs. Martinez.
our waiting list is a year long.
- [knocks on door]
- There's no hot water.
The plumber was here last
week. Call the plumber
- and get him back in here.
- I did. he can't come
- till Thursday.
- I'm sorry to interrupt you.
that-that... but
that's not a problem.
I-If it's a plumber
that you need.
I can literally get a
plumber here within the hour.
And it has no bearing
on Maria's mum at all.
that's just...
that-that's an easy fix.
'cause that's-that's what
we do. if that helps.
I'm happy to leave you a number.
[clears throat] Yeah.
His name's Dave.
and he's a magician. actually.
you'll really love him.
You know what. I noticed your
window when I come in as well.
I'm a bit of an OCD about that.
Uh. his brother Steve
is a. is a glazier.
He'll be all over that.
All right. you
tell him that Harry
told you to call.
you understand?
He owes me a favor. so
I doubt he'll charge.
That's my number. too. in
case there's any problems.
There won't be a problem.
Look. I don't want
to waste your time.
If anything comes up. please.
i-if you would just...
let us know.
Thank you.
Do you think we'll
hear from her?
- She'll call.
- [phone vibrates]
[attendant] Cup
of tea. Mr. Rusby?
[Rusby] Lovely.
♪ Slow. contemplative music
♪
[grunting]
[indistinct chatter]
- [shouting]
- [grunting]
♪
Are you okay. Harry?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm good.
Where are we at?
All right. thanks.
Stand by for my text.
[camera shutter clicks]
[camera shutter clicking]
♪ ominous music ♪
♪
[distorted grunting]
[door closes]
Czechs came through.
[Harry] I see.
- Where's Valjon?
- [sighs]
He's still in the container.
Okay.
[softly] All right.
- Cup of tea. Harry?
- No. you're all right. mate.
Has Bella called you?
She's not picking up.
No. mate.
I fucking swear.
she's up to something.
[scoffs] I just don't know what.
I told her the
house had been done
and she barely flinched.
It didn't mean anything to her.
Got any idea what it might be?
[Harry] No. mate.
I don't know.
Yeah. all right.
[grunts]
[Harry] Okay.
You good. yeah?
- Yeah. I'm good.
- All right.
[exhales]
[Harry] Hello. Valjon.
You remember. when
I first met you.
I said something to you.
Do you remember what I said?
Let me refresh
your memory. yeah?
I said. "If you
help the Harrigans.
the Harrigans will help you."
Yeah? Do you remember that?
Do you?
- Yeah.
- Right.
Well. you-you have not
helped the Harrigans.
Not-not at all. okay?
So now I. and Kevin here.
he's gonna lose his family.
I'm gonna lose my family.
Both of us are gonna die.
And others. yeah. thanks to you.
And Eddie. Okay?
So. I don't think it's very
fair that you don't share
in some of that joy.
Do you understand?
[Kevin] Here we are.
- How's that look?
- [gasping]
Mika. Rose.
- [cries softly]
- I had an aunt called Rose.
- [whispers] She was lovely.
- [sniffles]
[whimpering]
- Y-You kill my kids?
- [Harry] Hundred percent. mate.
- No. no. no. no!
- [gun clicks]
Fuck.
No. Please. please. please!
[Kevin] Harry. Harry.
- Here.
- Don't kill my kids.
- All right.
- Yeah. go on.
Are we sticking to the plan?
Yeah. yeah. mate.
Same page. why?
I thought. I thought you
were gonna fucking do him.
No. no. no. no. no.
Not yet. Not yet.
[whispering indistinctly]
[whispering continues]
[Kevin] No. he
ain't up to this.
- Up-up to what?
- Hey. no one's asked you yet.
You just wait your
turn. you cunt.
Look at this fucking
state of him.
- He ain't gonna do it.
- Well. he needs to...
[Valjon] Do what?
[Harry] Yeah. we just
got to keep fishing.
[Kevin] He's a fucking wreck.
[Harry] Keep pumping
him for some leverage.
You got him. mate.
[continues indistinctly]
Sorry. mate. computer says no.
- Okay.
- No. no. no! Please!
I'll do anything!
- Please. don't kill my kids.
- [Kevin] Harry. Harry. Harry.
- What did you just say?
- [crying] I'll do anything.
Please don't kill my
kids. Please. I beg you.
Do you mean that?
[breathing shakily]
Don't kill my kids.
[Harry] All right. Good man.
[Eddie groans]
Eddie.
[Seraphina exhales] Well.
Eddie. you've done it.
You've finally knocked
Brendan off top spot
for Harrigan
Family's Biggest Tit.
- Sorry. you are...?
- Don't try to be smart.
You've dropped this
family right in the shit.
This family?
Oh. you mean my family.
By the way. are you my
step aunt or half aunt?
It's just. I typed both into
Pornhub and nothing came up.
You better watch your mouth.
you cheeky little cunt.
- What. is that a new couch?
- And rug.
Courtesy of Archie.
Oh. Yeah. I hear the
old fart was a grass.
There's no way Archie was snide.
[Brendan] Not
according to Mum.
Mum says Harry got
hauled in next morning
and grilled all about
Archie's whereabouts.
How else would they know
unless he was back-channeling?
Eddie.
Nice to see you. you
knifey little twerp.
All right. Brenda.
I hear I have you to
thank for torpedoing
my entire week.
[Maeve] ♪ Will you
march with O'Neill ♪
♪ Through an Irish
battlefield? ♪
♪ For tonight we're going
to free old Wexford town ♪
Eddie stood up for his family.
Don't you listen to
them. my darling.
You. you. Eddie.
are the heart and
soul of the Harrigans.
The heart and soul.
No one outside the family
will ever understand that.
That's deeply moving. Maeve.
May I point out. you
married into this family.
Brendan and me. we share
actual Harrigan DNA.
Well. I wouldn't be so sure
about that. actually. Seraphina.
Old Pete Stringfellow told
me there was quite the queue
outside that toilet door.
[Eddie snickers]
[chuckles]
Don't listen to her. hmm?
Walk with me. Come on.
[tongue clicks] Come on.
Let's get your coat.
It's cold out here.
♪ Slow. pulsing music
What if he doesn't believe me?
That's the problem. innit?
You have to be convincing.
You have to convince him. yeah?
- W-What if I can't?
- Well. you have to.
There is no fucking
choice. that's the point.
Otherwise we get malleted. yeah?
He don't understand.
He don't get it. Look.
I don't like this. right?
One. he don't get it.
Two. if we take him to
Richie's right now. right.
Richie's gonna take one
look at him and think.
"He killed my son Tommy."
so what's he gonna do?
He's gonna fucking
kill his kids anyway.
So. what is the fucking point
in all of this? We might
as well just slot him
now. and the kids.
'cause he's fucking...
he's no use to us.
Listen to me. Hey.
If you do this for us.
then I promise.
when you leave here.
your kids will be swept up
and taken care of for
the rest of their lives.
- [Harry] Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Think about it.
Sweep up his kids.
look after them the
rest of his life. yeah?
Who's gonna do the
sweeping up? Me?
- Course.
- I have no doubt
that you could do that.
right. but look. look at him.
He's a fucking mess.
- You trust him?
- Yeah.
All right. You are one
lucky fucking cunt.
I do not trust you. yeah?
If you do not pull this
off. I will be watching you.
And seeing as I will be
doing the sweeping up. yeah.
I will also not be so
fucking benevolent.
It's on you.
Can I see my kids?
Can I s-speak to my kids?
No.
You understand.
[ragged exhale]
[ducks quacking]
She's a fucking bitch.
Well. your mother and
me... [laughs softly]
that was a bitter pill
for Maeve to swallow.
And then you came
along. That was hard.
I'll tell you what's
hard. Dad: Maeve.
She's hard to like.
Mm. [chuckles]
Yeah. she was 16 when I got
her pregnant with Brendan.
Her people run the
farm next to ours.
One night... [chuckles]
there was a knock at the door.
I assumed it was her
da with a shotgun.
I went to the
door. very nervous.
I opened it.
[laughs]
And I was right
about the shotgun.
but it wasn't her da
pointing it in my face.
it was Maeve.
Yeah. She's a hard woman. Maeve.
I'd just like a
bit of appreciation
for what I do for
this family. is all.
Yeah. come here now.
I appreciate you. I do.
Brendan came to me.
He's got a proposition.
- Oh. fuck.
- He says it's worth a bundle.
Yeah.
Well. we're gonna have to get
more clean money
in our accounts.
otherwise the banks
are gonna fuck us.
Do be careful. now.
That boy is about as useful
as a chocolate teapot.
- [laughs]
- Just hear him out.
but don't give him 50 pence
without coming to me first.
- Do you hear me now?
- Mm-hmm.
- Dad?
- Hmm?
Did Eddie kill Tommy Stevenson?
'Cause if I was Richie. there's
no one else in the frame.
It was him. wasn't it?
Richie will believe what
I want Richie to believe.
Nothing more. and nothing less.
[race announcer
speaking indistinctly]
[phone ringing]
[race announcer
continues over TV]
[phone continues ringing]
Yeah?
Richie. it's Harry.
Uh...
It's not good news. mate.
I've found Tommy.
[grunts]
[crying]
[coughing]
[moaning. panting]
♪ somber music ♪
[coughs]
[exhales sharply. sniffles]
Jesus Christ. Harry.
I do not like this.
Yeah. I'm not loving it.
We put him in front of Richie.
he could shop us
inside a minute.
- In ten seconds.
- Yeah. he could.
- All right. yeah?
- All right.
All right.
Do you think he's got this?
What you doing?
I told you I was followed.
[Kevin] Ah. fucking hell.
Right. I'll call you
when it's over. yeah?
All right.
Hey. there's a Mars bar
in the glove compartment.
It better be there
when you get back.
You don't need another
Mars bar. you fat cunt.
♪
[phone ringing]
Code.
[clears throat] Yeah.
what can I do you for?
Patch it through.
[Fisk] Where the fuck
are you going. Harry?
♪
[turn signal clicking]
[sighs]
Hello. Frisk.
Fuck.
[vehicle departing]
What now?
[phone chiming]
Yeah. Fisk.
Sir. Main switchboard just
received an anonymous call.
It's about the location
of Archie Hammond's body.
[sighs]
♪ tense music
[Valjon] I find him.
and I throw him in
the back of my car.
He tries to stab me. so
I take the knife off him.
He-he puts up a fight. so...
I stab him.
I stab him again.
I then put him in
the boot of my car
and I took him
back to my office.
where he bleeds to death.
I figure...
...I better get rid
of the body. so I...
...chop him up.
Do you have kids?
Yeah.
Where are those kids now?
Spain.
Not in Kevin
Harrigan's lockup. now?
No.
No. my wife.
she-she met someone else
and took off with my kids.
Yeah. that's tough.
[screaming]
Thank you for bringing
this man to me.
You can go now.
Me?
I'm gonna talk to
our friend here
very. very thoroughly.
And if I find a single
crack in his story.
the slightest flicker of doubt.
something that just
don't add up...
...then you'll
hear from me again.
But until then...
I'll sleep on it.
Until then...
I'll take your word for it. H.
- [crying softly]
- Olie?
Show him out.
[Olie] Come on.
[door opens]
[gasping. whimpering]
[door closes]
[moaning]
All right. my friend.
[footsteps approaching]
Let's begin.
[phone vibrating]
Did he buy it?
I don't know.
One thing's for sure.
he's gonna be going in
double hard on Valjon tonight.
If I know Valjon. which...
let's face it. mate...
I-I fucking don't. you know...
Does Dad know yet?
Nope. I think that might
be better coming from you.
Right. I've got to go
and meet someone. yeah?
Call Conrad.
[doors lock]
♪ tense music
[knocks on door]
[sniffles]
Hi.
Kevin texted.
Said the coast is clear.
Did you answer him?
- You want a mezcal?
- No. I've got to get back.
What do you need?
I fucked up.
How?
I brought Antoine to
meet my father today.
My father promised to introduce
him to the prime minister.
to a high pile of the
great and the good.
for a price. obviously.
a high price.
- And?
- And I filmed him.
Or rather. Antoine did.
He's made a copy and
now he's threatening
to tell my dad what I
did unless I pay him.
Right.
Well. um...
couldn't this have
waited till tomorrow?
Not if I'm going
to get any sleep.
Where is Antoine?
- At the Savoy.
- Hmm.
Now. this is very dangerous.
As dangerous as getting
my house blown up?
This is the kind of danger
the family will not like.
I will take care of Antoine.
Why do you do this?
- Do what?
- This.
Run around like a blue-arsed fly
for an insane. disloyal monster.
We're all monsters. Bella.
I can't stand mine.
So leave.
I can't.
Then we have that in common.
You're common.
Do you travel?
Have you heard of
parallel universes?
There's a world in which
everything is exactly the same
except you're a
dog and I'm a cat.
In another world. I'm
a cat. you're a dog.
and mice are lions and bread
is blue. and so on and so on.
And in one universe.
there's a world
in which there are no Harrigans.
no Stevensons. no
Jan and no Kevin.
and you lean in and kiss me now.
How did it feel?
Call Kevin.
I'll take care of Antoine.
♪ Slow. dramatic music
[vehicle doors unlock]
[sniffles]
[distant siren wailing]
[sighs]
[drill whirring]
♪
[camera shutter clicks]
Hello. Archie.
♪ "Dark Days" by Yard Act
♪ The truth was sold ♪
♪ That's where the
trail goes cold ♪
♪ My shoulders shudder
at the thought ♪
♪ Of puffing my chest out
as I walk home alone ♪
♪ At least when I meet my maker.
I'll embrace all my mistakes ♪
♪ As I descend into
the bowels of hell ♪
♪ With a shit-eating grin ♪
- ♪ On my face ♪
- ♪ Dark days ♪
♪ It's a never-ending
cycle of abuse ♪
- ♪ Dark days ♪
- ♪ I have the blues ♪
♪ And I can't shake them loose ♪
- ♪ Dark days ♪
- ♪ I have the blues ♪
♪ And I can't shake them loose ♪
- ♪ Dark days ♪
- ♪ It's a never-ending cycle ♪
♪ Of abuse ♪
♪ Was skeptic due to how
the media had depicted you ♪
♪